<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[My Octopress Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-23T18:40:18-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Your Name]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 10 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/24/week-10/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-24T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/24/week-10</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2015 -08-24- This is my 10th week in my YWEB class.This week was wonderful, each day I have been learning a lot. I am feel that my skills in tech are development. I am feel very happy to be in this class.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 9 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/17/week-9/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-17T12:00:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/17/week-9</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>Week</h1>

<p>2015-08-17 this is my 9 week of my journal. After I finished some of my homework, like Chapter 3 JavaScript CssCross County and start doing my portfolio I feel more confident with the learned my dificulties and errors  I feel more confident in my class. I  also thank my classmates Jane, Katty and Mr. Jim and tutors tutors  who come on Saturdays to help us</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 8 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/08/week-8/"/>
    <updated>2015-08-08T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/08/08/week-8</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>Week 8</h1>

<p>2015-08-08 this is my 8 week of my journal. After I finished some of my homework, like Chapter 3 JavaScript CssCross County and start doing my portfolio I feel more confident with the learned my dificulties and errors  I feel more confident in my class. I  also thank my classmates Jane, Katty and Mr. Jim and tutors tutors  who come on Saturdays to help us</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 7 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/31/week-7/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-31T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/31/week-7</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2015.07.31 - blogpost.md
This is my 7th week in my YWeb class. This week was very very hard for me. I almost quit because my husband was disappointed that I spend so many hours working at Perkins restaurant with other students to cough up my work, and I used to arrive home after 12am and he said he didn&rsquo;t see me at home as a wife. Well teacher, I am here doing my best in my work, and thank you for helping me when I came to you with work questions. This week, I am working in CSS Zen Garden and a little bit in my portfolio, and also trying to finish Code School Foundations.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 6 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/week-6/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-24T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/24/week-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2015.07.24 -blogpost.md
This is my 6th week of my journal. On this week, I feel very busy doing the Java Script chapter 3 and I am still working in that, but also I was doing another project that it is the portfolio. I worked very hard I am trying to send my work on time but it sounds like I couldn&rsquo;t make it.  I keep going and do my work as much I can.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 5 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/17/week-5/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-17T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/17/week-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2015.07.17
This is my fifth week of my journal.
My week was very busy. I worked in Front End Foundations Level 1, and I finished my work on Formations Level 1 and 2. This week was very hard trying to finish my work from Java Script- Chapter 2. I work most of the time at night doing my chapter 2 to be done I spend most of my life working to try to complete my assigned work on time.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 4 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/14/week-4/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-14T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/14/week-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my 4th Journal
The Madison + UX was very educational for me, I really appreciated to have the opportunity to attend the presentation. I have a better idea on how much I can do if I continue to study the technology (the new world).</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 3 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/03/week-3/"/>
    <updated>2015-07-03T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/07/03/week-3</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>week 3blog post
My week was very hard to learn the chapter 02 but I have help from my classmates like Brandon, Elizabeth, Maria and Akbar.  They were very patient with me. Also I like the Project management, it was very interactive and I have an opportunity to learn better.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 2 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/week-2/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-26T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/26/week-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today I finish my work book chapter 01
I set up my Blog post and Prey whit LuLu help Thank You.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Week 1 Blogpost]]></title>
    <link href="http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/week-1/"/>
    <updated>2015-06-19T16:42:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://tareas-1954.github.io/blog/blog/2015/06/19/week-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  This is my practice with my tutor Zach</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
